<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FreeYourSoul</title>
    <link>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FreeYourSoul</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:07:40 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Back to bloging</title>
      <link>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/posts/back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:07:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/posts/back/</guid>
      <description>Back to blogging  Link to heading   Hey! I finally found a glimpse of motivation to come back into blogging. About C++, architecture and other things. At first I may repost all my previously created blogs in this github page based blog, as I lost my previous website due to inactivity.
I would like to thank some of you who supported me into going back into blogging. Some liked my blogs, made me very happy, and now I am back to write more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, my name is Quentin Balland, 29 years old.
I am a french c++ developer currently living in Switzerland and working as a C++ software engineer.
I like software development which made me want to begin this blog and go into development experimentation while sharing it with you. With the hope I can make people learn from my experience but mostly to learn from you all and get the better of your eventual comment about my content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>conference report : ACCU2019</title>
      <link>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/posts/conf_report_accu_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:07:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/posts/conf_report_accu_2019/</guid>
      <description>Conference Report: ACCU 2019  Link to heading   I had the pleasure to attend to the ACCU2019 in Bristol which was my first cpp centred conference (the first of a long series I hope :p) and it was amazing in a different aspect.
It is a 4 days conference that occurs every year between March and April in the Marriott hotel in Bristol.
Amazing people, very inclusive and easy to talk to everyone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FyS : frst architecture</title>
      <link>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/posts/fys_2_first_architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:07:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/posts/fys_2_first_architecture/</guid>
      <description>The First architecture part-1  Link to heading   Data-Oriented Design  Link to heading   We directly begin with one of the topics I took most of my time working on. For the people not familiar with Data Oriented Design (DoD), I will try explaining it in this post. But I will also give several links to content that are, I think, needed in order to grasp the importance and power of DoD in C++.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FyS : introduction and idea</title>
      <link>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/posts/fys_1_intro_idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:07:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/posts/fys_1_intro_idea/</guid>
      <description>FyS : introduction and idea  Link to heading   What is FreeYourSoul concept, where did the idea come from ?  Link to heading   Basically, the idea was just to have a big project, that would force me to cover and explore multiple subjects into depth, and to improve in a lot of different aspect of software engineering and in the C++ language itself. The project began in late 2017, and I wanted to try the new features of the C++ standard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me on mastodon
You can find me on linkedin as well : https://ch.linkedin.com/in/quentin-balland-68316252</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://freeyoursoul.github.io/blog/projects/</guid>
      <description>Nothing to see here&amp;hellip; Move along!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
